[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 3, "question": "What went through my mind when I fell down?", "qSentId": 2}, {"answer": "I think -- well, I think probably it's going to be the memory that everybody is going to remember, and that's Jennifer Lawrence, you know, tripping as she goes up.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "What was -- what was your most memorable moment of the whole day, do you think?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's a little unfair.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Why is she getting a bit of a kicking?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "You know, it's funny because we have this conversation at the show all the time because I'm always in defense of her because I have loved interviewing her and I think she's very sweet ad she --", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "Why are we so bitchy about Anne Hathaway?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "I was apparently trending worldwide on Twitter, I was told momentarily.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "And what were you thinking?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "No, not really.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "Are you -- are you leaping around the room, are you making acceptance speeches?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "It was very unusual.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "I did a cover story about Seth in 2005 for \"TV Guide\" and look, I've always, always found him to be a very interesting character.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "Is there any truth to that?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm a big fan of Seth's.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "I mean, Krista, are you a fan of Seth MacFarlane last night?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "I know, it's a lack of sleep.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "How could you forget him?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "You like to see people uncomfortable?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "Yes, it is kind of true.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "That's how you have to react to these things, isn't it?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "(SMILING)", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "What's your loser face?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "No, that I haven't.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Do you practice your loser face just in case the camera pans straight to you?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "No, I just didn't think of it, but I'll start right now.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Do you think it's bad luck?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Just kind of a glazed smile, you know, yes, followed by some kind of protein bar.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "Have you got one?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Then I giggle.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Give me the face?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "You know what, very interesting.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "Who was the Piers Morgan choice?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "From my vantage point, absolutely not.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "Should she have been there at all?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "Let me fill you in on what the first lady's strategy has been on this kind of thing.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Obviously, she can, Piers.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Why are we getting so exercised about it, Donny?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "If she ever does that, I will come back on your show and I will physically eat my book one page at a time.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "I actually don't think Americans are victims here.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "If you were advising them, Washington Incorporated, about their brand, how do they get the message that America is sick and tired of this kind of behavior?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Why does America need to have this astronomical ongoing defense budget when you have more pressing things at home to worry about?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "We're going to attend a candlelight ceremony here in New York.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Sybrina, how are you planning to commemorate Trayvon's life and death tomorrow?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "From all the senseless gun violence that's been happening since our son's tragic loss, it's -- it's time for America to take a look at our gun laws, do something with the gun laws, take a look at the people that are purchasing guns, people that they are giving gun licenses to, because it's just too much senseless violence, just overwhelming the homes right now.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "Where do you see it right now?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, you try to be very open and honest about them.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "How do you tackle that kind of mentality in light of this debate about Stand Your Ground?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "A difficult question for you, Sybrina, but I want to put it to you anyway.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Because if he's not held accountable, what message does that send to the next child that's killed, unarmed, on the ground?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "Well, that's something that we have always asked for.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "In other words, if at the end of this trial George Zimmerman is exonerated of illegally killing your son, would you be prepared to publicly accept that verdict?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "I think it is interesting, Piers, that we heard the official statement that says the Holy Father is sick, that the Holy Father is frail.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "What did you make of that, first of all?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "Well, I take the Pope on his word.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "When you put it all together, where are we left here, do you think?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "I think it is for those who are called to be monks, to be religious.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "Is celibacy really any longer a sensible thing for the Catholic church to enforce upon the priesthood?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "Well, let me respond to the statement about homosexuals in the clergy.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 710, "question": "I mean, is it time, in short, we had a more modern thinking Pope for the modern era?", "qSentId": 709}, {"answer": "I actually don't think Americans are victims here.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 749, "question": "If you were advising them, Washington Incorporated, about their brand, how do they get the message that America is sick and tired of this kind of behavior?", "qSentId": 748}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 764, "question": "Why does America need to have this astronomical ongoing defense budget when you have more pressing things at home to worry about?", "qSentId": 763}, {"answer": "We're going to attend a candlelight ceremony here in New York.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 794, "question": "Sybrina, how are you planning to commemorate Trayvon's life and death tomorrow?", "qSentId": 793}, {"answer": "From all the senseless gun violence that's been happening since our son's tragic loss, it's -- it's time for America to take a look at our gun laws, do something with the gun laws, take a look at the people that are purchasing guns, people that they are giving gun licenses to, because it's just too much senseless violence, just overwhelming the homes right now.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 803, "question": "Where do you see it right now?", "qSentId": 802}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, you try to be very open and honest about them.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 815, "question": "How do you tackle that kind of mentality in light of this debate about Stand Your Ground?", "qSentId": 814}, {"answer": "A difficult question for you, Sybrina, but I want to put it to you anyway.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 826, "question": "Because if he's not held accountable, what message does that send to the next child that's killed, unarmed, on the ground?", "qSentId": 825}, {"answer": "Well, that's something that we have always asked for.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 830, "question": "In other words, if at the end of this trial George Zimmerman is exonerated of illegally killing your son, would you be prepared to publicly accept that verdict?", "qSentId": 829}, {"answer": "I think it is interesting, Piers, that we heard the official statement that says the Holy Father is sick, that the Holy Father is frail.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 855, "question": "What did you make of that, first of all?", "qSentId": 854}, {"answer": "Well, I take the Pope on his word.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 870, "question": "When you put it all together, where are we left here, do you think?", "qSentId": 869}, {"answer": "I think it is for those who are called to be monks, to be religious.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 894, "question": "Is celibacy really any longer a sensible thing for the Catholic church to enforce upon the priesthood?", "qSentId": 893}, {"answer": "EESE: Well, let me respond to the statement about homosexuals in the clergy.", "docId": "130225pmt", "aSentId": 907, "question": "I mean, is it time, in short, we had a more modern thinking Pope for the modern era?", "qSentId": 906}]